{"question":"17ч 15мин + 3ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 5мин - 2ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 29мин + 2ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 57мин - 2ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 36мин + 1ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 35мин - 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 55мин + 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 20мин - 3ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 37мин + 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 6мин - 1ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 47мин + 3ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 37мин - 3ч 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 19мин + 3ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 42мин - 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 24мин + 1ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 35мин - 3ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 46мин + 3ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 43мин - 1ч 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 34мин + 1ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 33мин - 2ч 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 45мин + 3ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 13мин - 3ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 25мин + 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 22мин - 2ч 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч + 3ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 21мин - 2ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 42мин + 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 20мин - 3ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 29мин + 2ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 17мин - 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 26мин + 1ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 49мин - 3ч 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 11мин + 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 22мин - 2ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 2мин + 3ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 6мин - 1ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 6мин + 2ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 49мин - 1ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 8мин + 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 24мин - 2ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 58мин + 3ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 46мин - 3ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 26мин + 3ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 21мин - 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 59мин + 1ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 42мин - 3ч 34мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 20мин + 1ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 59мин - 2ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 36мин + 3ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 23мин - 1ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 18мин + 1ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 41мин - 3ч 34мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 6мин + 1ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 18мин - 2ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 46мин + 2ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 5мин - 3ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 25мин + 2ч 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 35мин - 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 15мин + 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 53мин - 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 13мин + 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 49мин - 3ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 40мин + 3ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 56мин - 2ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 48мин + 2ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 50мин - 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 55мин + 3ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 39мин - 2ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 40мин + 3ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 59мин - 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 6мин + 3ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 17мин - 2ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 16мин + 3ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 44мин - 3ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 15мин + 2ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 26мин - 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 14мин + 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 24мин - 1ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 55мин + 2ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 40мин - 2ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 57мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 57мин - 2ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 28мин + 2ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 14мин - 2ч 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 24мин + 3ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 45мин - 3ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 10мин + 2ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч - 2ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 30мин + 1ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 35мин - 1ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 8мин + 1ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 3мин - 3ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 18мин + 2ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 13мин - 2ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 52мин + 1ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 5мин - 1ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 13мин + 3ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 47мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 50мин + 3ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 41мин - 1ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 55мин + 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 38мин - 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 31мин + 3ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 1мин - 3ч 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 40мин + 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 54мин - 1ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 36мин + 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 51мин - 3ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 2мин + 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 1мин - 3ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 51мин + 1ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 55мин - 4ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 6мин + 3ч 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 34мин - 1ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 55мин + 3ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 49мин - 2ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 18мин + 3ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 5мин - 1ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 22мин + 3ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 55мин - 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 55мин + 2ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 36мин - 1ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 39мин + 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 14мин - 3ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 7мин + 3ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 7мин - 1ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 29мин + 3ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 55мин - 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 50мин + 2ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 26мин - 1ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 35мин + 1ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 27мин - 3ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 33мин + 2ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 33мин - 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 15мин + 3ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 42мин - 2ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 38мин + 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 24мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 55мин + 3ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 51мин - 1ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 25мин + 3ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 59мин - 1ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 19мин + 2ч 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 12мин - 1ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 26мин + 2ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 27мин - 3ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 57мин + 1ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 21мин - 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 13мин + 2ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 57мин - 3ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 49мин + 2ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 38мин - 2ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 54мин + 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч - 1ч 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 56мин + 2ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 14мин - 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 42мин + 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 2мин - 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 36мин + 3ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 25мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 55мин + 3ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 1мин - 1ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 53мин + 2ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 27мин - 1ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 58мин + 3ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 12мин - 2ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 11мин + 2ч 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 35мин - 2ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч + 2ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 40мин - 3ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 16мин + 2ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 9мин - 3ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 4мин + 2ч 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 38мин - 2ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 28мин + 1ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 23мин - 3ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 17мин + 1ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 47мин - 1ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 44мин + 1ч 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 28мин - 3ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч + 1ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 58мин - 3ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 59мин + 1ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 37мин - 3ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 36мин + 1ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 9мин - 1ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 13мин + 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 57мин - 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 59мин + 2ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 36мин - 2ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 55мин + 1ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 30мин - 1ч 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 44мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 53мин - 2ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 44мин + 1ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 14мин - 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 50мин + 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 54мин - 2ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 11мин + 3ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 45мин - 3ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 42мин + 3ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 46мин - 2ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 22мин + 3ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 31мин - 1ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 14мин + 2ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 17мин - 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 27мин + 3ч 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 6мин - 2ч 34мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 27мин + 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 23мин - 2ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 48мин + 2ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 41мин - 1ч 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 14мин + 2ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 16мин - 1ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 22мин + 1ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 26мин - 2ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 22мин + 3ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 23мин - 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 15мин + 2ч 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 38мин - 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 46мин + 2ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 40мин - 2ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 4мин + 2ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 31мин - 3ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 47мин + 3ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 35мин - 3ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 3мин + 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 11мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 17мин + 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 19мин - 1ч 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 5мин + 3ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 9мин - 1ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 18мин + 2ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч - 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 12мин + 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 55мин - 3ч 26мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 23мин + 3ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 41мин - 2ч 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 4мин + 2ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 6мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 3мин + 3ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 25мин - 1ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 10мин + 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч - 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 8мин + 2ч 26мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 2мин - 3ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 46мин + 1ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 12мин - 26мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч + 3ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 41мин - 2ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 27мин + 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 18мин - 3ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 22мин + 1ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 14мин - 2ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 39мин + 1ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 50мин - 1ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 44мин + 2ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 9мин - 2ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 26мин + 3ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 46мин - 2ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 19мин + 1ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 41мин - 3ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 51мин + 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 20мин - 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 14мин + 4ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 56мин - 2ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 19мин + 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 16мин - 3ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 11мин + 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 44мин - 3ч 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 6мин + 3ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 28мин - 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 20мин + 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 26мин - 3ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 2мин + 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 10мин - 2ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 17мин + 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 41мин - 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 1мин + 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 42мин - 3ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 33мин + 1ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 33мин - 2ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 22мин + 3ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 19мин - 1ч 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 36мин + 3ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 53мин - 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 30мин + 2ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 33мин - 2ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 29мин + 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 31мин - 2ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 56мин + 1ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 41мин - 1ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 17мин + 2ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 20мин - 2ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 24мин + 3ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 53мин - 2ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 16мин + 2ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 54мин - 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 46мин + 2ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 32мин - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 19мин + 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 40мин - 1ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 25мин + 3ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 55мин - 4ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 47мин + 1ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 25мин - 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 40мин + 3ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 16мин - 1ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 32мин + 2ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 11мин - 1ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 3мин + 1ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 38мин - 1ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 16мин + 2ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 26мин - 1ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 9мин + 3ч 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 33мин - 2ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 52мин + 3ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 18мин - 2ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 43мин + 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 51мин - 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 45мин + 1ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 34мин - 2ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 7мин + 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч - 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 18мин + 2ч 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 6мин - 3ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 31мин + 2ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 8мин - 2ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 56мин + 3ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 59мин - 3ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 30мин + 3ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 41мин - 1ч 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 18мин + 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 51мин - 3ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 36мин + 3ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 44мин - 2ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 53мин + 1ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 7мин - 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 34мин + 1ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 32мин - 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 32мин + 2ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 51мин - 1ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 25мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 18мин - 1ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 10мин + 3ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 39мин - 2ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 26мин + 3ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 48мин - 3ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 18мин + 2ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 55мин - 2ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 12мин + 2ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 57мин - 2ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 7мин + 3ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 51мин - 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 39мин + 3ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 20мин - 3ч 26мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч + 2ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 52мин - 1ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 45мин + 3ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 20мин - 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 52мин + 2ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 11мин - 1ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 15мин + 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 47мин - 3ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч + 1ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 15мин - 1ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 45мин + 1ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 48мин - 1ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 32мин + 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 50мин - 2ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 42мин + 1ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 50мин - 3ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 21мин + 1ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 41мин - 1ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 34мин + 3ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 58мин - 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 18мин + 1ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 20мин - 1ч 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 27мин + 2ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 3мин - 2ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 17мин + 3ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 24мин - 1ч 26мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 29мин + 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 23мин - 3ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 24мин + 1ч 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 38мин - 2ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 5мин + 3ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 34мин - 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 11мин + 2ч 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 19мин - 3ч 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 52мин + 2ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 21мин - 3ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 59мин + 2ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 4мин - 3ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 57мин + 3ч 34мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 12мин - 2ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 7мин + 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 50мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 20мин + 2ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 1мин - 3ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 44мин + 1ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 42мин - 2ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 56мин + 3ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 43мин - 3ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 18мин + 3ч 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 45мин - 3ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 24мин + 1ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 19мин - 2ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 45мин + 3ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 47мин - 1ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 9мин + 1ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 36мин - 1ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 29мин + 2ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 35мин - 1ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 40мин + 2ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 5мин - 3ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 14мин + 2ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 30мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 18мин + 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 27мин - 2ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 28мин + 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 56мин - 2ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 55мин + 2ч 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 56мин - 3ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 57мин + 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 33мин - 2ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 2мин + 3ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 11мин - 1ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 56мин + 3ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 51мин - 1ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 18мин + 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 47мин - 1ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 15мин + 2ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 18мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 23мин + 3ч 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 5мин - 1ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 25мин + 3ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 37мин - 1ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 17мин + 1ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 53мин - 1ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 9мин + 1ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 58мин - 2ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 7мин + 2ч 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч - 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 5мин + 2ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 14мин - 1ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 15мин + 2ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 44мин - 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 18мин + 3ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 22мин - 3ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 43мин + 2ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 27мин - 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 17мин + 1ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 6мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 29мин + 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 52мин - 1ч 26мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 2мин + 3ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 53мин - 3ч 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 46мин + 3ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 8мин - 1ч 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 1мин + 1ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 25мин - 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 3мин + 3ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 28мин - 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 49мин + 2ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 16мин - 3ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 23мин + 3ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 14мин - 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 26мин + 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 51мин - 3ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 40мин + 1ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч - 1ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 34мин + 1ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 59мин - 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 30мин + 2ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 13мин - 2ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 25мин + 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 40мин - 1ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч + 3ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 45мин - 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 35мин + 1ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 26мин - 2ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 54мин + 2ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 49мин - 1ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 11мин + 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч - 26мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 8мин + 2ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 14мин - 3ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 1мин + 2ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 40мин - 3ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 50мин + 2ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 1мин - 1ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 53мин + 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 19мин - 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 37мин + 1ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 51мин - 2ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 43мин + 1ч 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 16мин - 2ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 2мин + 3ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 6мин - 1ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч + 3ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 13мин - 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 47мин + 2ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 41мин - 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 14мин + 3ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 53мин - 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 35мин + 2ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 40мин - 3ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 43мин + 2ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 16мин - 2ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 19мин + 3ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 4мин - 1ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 28мин + 2ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 13мин - 1ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 21мин + 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 29мин - 3ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 17мин + 3ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 47мин - 1ч 34мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 13мин + 3ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 6мин - 1ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 14мин + 3ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 44мин - 2ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 26мин + 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 9мин - 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 36мин + 1ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 36мин - 3ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 22мин + 34мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 55мин - 2ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 55мин + 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 34мин - 1ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 27мин + 3ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 18мин - 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 10мин + 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 43мин - 3ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 5мин + 3ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"23", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 49мин - 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 3мин + 2ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 38мин - 1ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 42мин + 1ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 58мин - 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 31мин + 3ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 49мин - 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 6мин + 1ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 37мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 44мин + 2ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 4мин - 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 33мин + 1ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 33мин - 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 35мин + 2ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 52мин - 2ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 7мин + 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 59мин - 2ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 51мин + 2ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 35мин - 1ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 56мин + 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 27мин - 2ч 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 30мин + 2ч 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 37мин - 2ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 31мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 52мин - 3ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 44мин + 3ч 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 33мин - 3ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 35мин + 1ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 7мин - 3ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 59мин + 3ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 42мин - 3ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 49мин + 1ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 47мин - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 15мин + 2ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 31мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 29мин + 2ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 44мин - 3ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 19мин + 1ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 26мин - 1ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 20мин + 1ч 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 9мин - 1ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 5мин + 3ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 3мин - 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 24мин + 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 1мин - 3ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 57мин + 2ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 14мин - 2ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 49мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 52мин - 3ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 45мин + 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 40мин - 3ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 50мин + 2ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 4мин - 1ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 59мин + 3ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 47мин - 2ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 8мин + 3ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 26мин - 2ч 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 19мин + 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 59мин - 2ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 55мин + 1ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 19мин - 1ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 30мин + 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 12мин - 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 58мин + 3ч 34мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 53мин - 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 24мин + 2ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 35мин - 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 2мин + 2ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 46мин - 1ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 41мин + 3ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 51мин - 2ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 58мин + 1ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 5мин - 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 29мин + 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 38мин - 3ч 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 12мин + 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 53мин - 2ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 3мин + 1ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 49мин - 3ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 11мин + 3ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 35мин - 3ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 23мин + 2ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 56мин - 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 33мин + 1ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 46мин - 2ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 6мин + 3ч 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 3мин - 1ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 47мин + 2ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 45мин - 1ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч + 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 37мин - 3ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 36мин + 1ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 11мин - 3ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 55мин + 3ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 2мин - 2ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 8мин + 3ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 21мин - 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 38мин + 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 39мин - 2ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 43мин + 3ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 56мин - 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 33мин + 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 14мин - 3ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 5мин + 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 48мин - 1ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 12мин + 2ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 15мин - 2ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 19мин + 3ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 39мин - 3ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 35мин + 3ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 30мин - 3ч 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 47мин + 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 58мин - 2ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 18мин + 3ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 7мин - 2ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 51мин + 2ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 51мин - 1ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 25мин + 3ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 48мин - 3ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 8мин + 2ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 50мин - 2ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 41мин + 1ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 37мин - 1ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 35мин + 3ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 37мин - 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 26мин + 1ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 54мин - 1ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 41мин + 1ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 45мин - 2ч 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 47мин + 3ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 33мин - 2ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 53мин + 1ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 10мин - 2ч 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 8мин + 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 4мин - 1ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 2мин + 1ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 5мин - 3ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 56мин + 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 1мин - 2ч 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 20мин + 1ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 10мин - 1ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 38мин + 2ч 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 27мин - 3ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 16мин + 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 14мин - 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 35мин + 1ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 44мин - 2ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 47мин + 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч - 2ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 59мин + 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 48мин - 2ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 5мин + 2ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 45мин - 2ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 55мин + 3ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 54мин - 1ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч + 1ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 45мин - 1ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 53мин + 3ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 7мин - 3ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 34мин + 3ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 6мин - 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 5мин + 2ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 11мин - 2ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч + 3ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 45мин - 2ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 58мин + 1ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 49мин - 2ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 40мин + 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 23мин - 1ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 27мин + 3ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 21мин - 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 55мин + 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 44мин - 2ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 3мин + 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 19мин - 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 17мин + 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 42мин - 1ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 41мин + 1ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 51мин - 3ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 47мин + 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 58мин - 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 1мин + 1ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 14мин - 2ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 55мин + 3ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 12мин - 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 15мин + 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 48мин - 1ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 22мин + 3ч 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 4мин - 1ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 42мин + 3ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 1мин - 1ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 2мин + 1ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 57мин - 3ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 33мин + 1ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 5мин - 3ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 42мин + 3ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 11мин - 1ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 36мин + 3ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 17мин - 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 44мин + 3ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 59мин - 3ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 39мин + 1ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч - 2ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 21мин + 1ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 12мин - 2ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 44мин + 1ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 13мин - 3ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 10мин + 2ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 32мин - 1ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 31мин + 1ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 24мин - 1ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 33мин + 2ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 6мин - 2ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 28мин + 1ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 37мин - 2ч 16мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 48мин + 1ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 16мин - 2ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 2мин + 2ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 37мин - 2ч 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 6мин + 4ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 40мин - 3ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 31мин + 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 13мин - 3ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 16мин + 1ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 23мин - 1ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 31мин + 2ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 4мин - 1ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 7мин + 1ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 48мин - 2ч 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 9мин + 3ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 48мин - 3ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 25мин + 2ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 36мин - 3ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 5мин + 3ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 31мин - 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 41мин + 4ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 38мин - 3ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 3мин + 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 24мин - 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 20мин + 3ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 29мин - 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 56мин + 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 52мин - 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 58мин + 1ч 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 5мин - 1ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 44мин + 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 59мин - 3ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 57мин + 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 45мин - 1ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 16мин + 2ч 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 59мин - 1ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 3мин + 3ч 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 27мин - 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 42мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 6мин - 1ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 4мин + 2ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 35мин - 1ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 23мин + 3ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 41мин - 2ч 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 51мин + 3ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 23мин - 3ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 44мин + 3ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 54мин - 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 31мин + 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 57мин - 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 37мин + 2ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 27мин - 2ч 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 49мин + 2ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 35мин - 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 29мин + 1ч 49мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 50мин - 1ч 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 33мин + 1ч 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 27мин - 1ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 10мин + 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 3мин - 2ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 18мин + 2ч 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 3мин - 3ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 43мин + 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 25мин - 26мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"22ч 4мин + 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 11мин - 3ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 38мин + 3ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 42мин - 2ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 31мин + 3ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 12мин - 2ч 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 47мин + 1ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 41мин - 2ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 52мин + 2ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 35мин - 3ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 59мин + 3ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 17мин - 1ч 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 44мин + 3ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 54мин - 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 19мин + 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 29мин - 3ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 48мин + 1ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 16мин - 3ч 26мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 54мин + 2ч 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 34мин - 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 7мин + 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 45мин - 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 54мин + 1ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 25мин - 3ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 46мин + 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 18мин - 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 50мин + 2ч 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 46мин - 2ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 35мин + 1ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 30мин - 3ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 28мин + 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 45мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 40мин + 2ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 57мин - 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 3мин + 1ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 9мин - 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 26мин + 3ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 7мин - 2ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 31мин + 2ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 25мин - 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 11мин + 3ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 30мин - 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 49мин + 1ч 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 38мин - 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 51мин + 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 9мин - 3ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 10мин + 2ч 41мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 40мин - 2ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 39мин + 1ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"23ч - 2ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 1мин + 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 59мин - 3ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 25мин + 1ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 54мин - 3ч 57мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 52мин + 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 18мин - 2ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 2мин + 2ч 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 4мин - 3ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 8мин + 2ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 17мин - 1ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 24мин + 1ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 34мин - 2ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 58мин + 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 57мин - 3ч 47мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 5мин + 3ч 11мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 31мин - 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 53мин + 1ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 7мин - 2ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 8мин + 1ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 28мин - 2ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 32мин + 2ч 42мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 35мин - 3ч 39мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 22мин + 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 40мин - 3ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 39мин + 1ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 37мин - 3ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 17мин + 1ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 18мин - 2ч 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 46мин + 2ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 58мин - 2ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 40мин + 3ч 29мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 54мин - 1ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 48мин + 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 31мин - 1ч 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 28мин + 3ч 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 26мин - 1ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 5мин + 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 54мин - 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 31мин + 3ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 22мин - 1ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 16мин + 4ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 1мин - 3ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 53мин + 1ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 30мин - 2ч 8мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 54мин + 2ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 1мин - 1ч 18мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 10мин + 2ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 20мин - 3ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 23мин + 17мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 34мин - 2ч 24мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 22мин + 1ч 23мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 39мин - 2ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 46мин + 3ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 7мин - 2ч 34мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 56мин + 3ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 26мин - 51мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 3мин + 3ч 2мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 29мин - 2ч 27мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 2мин + 3ч 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 55мин - 1ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 3мин + 3ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 8мин - 3ч 34мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 46мин + 3ч 7мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 46мин - 1ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 25мин + 3ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 4мин - 2ч 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 31мин + 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"20", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 41мин - 1ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 57мин + 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 25мин - 2ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 36мин + 1ч 28мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 4мин - 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 46мин + 2ч 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 58мин - 3ч 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 12мин + 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 2мин - 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 3мин + 1ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 47мин - 2ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 36мин + 2ч 59мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 9мин - 1ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 23мин + 1ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 27мин - 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 57мин + 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 6мин - 1ч 3мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 8мин + 22мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 29мин - 3ч 46мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 20мин + 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 56мин - 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 37мин + 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 41мин - 54мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 15мин + 2ч 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 50мин - 1ч 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 12мин + 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 53мин - 3ч 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"12ч 43мин + 2ч 33мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"13ч 37мин - 1ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 57мин + 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 33мин - 2ч 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 27мин + 3ч 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 29мин - 2ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 9мин + 1ч 38мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 30мин - 4ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 4мин + 2ч 12мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 43мин - 3ч 48мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 39мин + 37мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 21мин - 3ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 59мин + 3ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 7мин - 1ч 9мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 24мин + 14мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 53мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 27мин + 1мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 8мин - 2ч 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 34мин + 2ч 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"19ч 42мин - 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 14мин + 2ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"20ч 13мин - 3ч 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 58мин + 4мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 17мин - 2ч 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 43мин + 19мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 30мин - 1ч 21мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"14", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 8мин + 1ч 31мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 20мин - 2ч 44мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 34мин + 3ч 36мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"18ч 42мин - 2ч 56мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"15ч 16мин + 32мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 19мин - 1ч 13мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 12мин + 43мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 15мин - 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"21ч 54мин + 1ч 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"23", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"16ч 14мин - 3ч 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"12", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 5мин + 2ч 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"11ч 27мин - 3ч 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"17ч 53мин + 6мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"14ч 24мин - 52мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"13", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 25мин + 58мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 29мин - 1ч 53мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
